The War is a drama, war film directed by Jon Avnet.
The son of a Vietnam War Veteran must deal with neighborhood bullies as well as his dad's
post-traumatic stress disorder while growing up in the deep south in the 1970's.
Stu Simmons, played by Elijah Wood.
Stephen Simmons, played by Kevin Costner.
Lois Simmons, played by Mare Winningham.
Lidia Joanne Simmons, played by Lexi Randall.
Elvadine, played by LaToya Chisholm.
Billy Lipnicki, played by Christopher Fennell.
The War is a 1994 American drama film directed by Jon Avnet and
starring Elijah Wood, Kevin Costner, and Mare Winningham.
It is a coming of age tale set in Mississippi in the 1970s.
Despite a weak box-office opening and negative reviews, the film
gained praise from critics for Wood's performance.
The film explores themes of vietnam veteran, bullying, kids.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.